You've reached the end of
the deep learning module.
Congratulations.
&gt;&gt; Roy you sounded just
like Sebastian right there.
&gt;&gt; Thank you,
I try to be just like Sebastian.
So do you feel like a deep
learning expert now?
&gt;&gt; Well I wouldn't
necessarily say expert, but
I think I know what tools I've got.
All right, I think you're ready to
build a behavioral cloning network.
The team at Udacity has built an awesome
simulator for you .It's going to be
your job to drive your car around
the track, collect the data and
then train the deep neural network
to do the driving for you.
So How would you approach
this kind of problem?
&gt;&gt; Well I guess I know.
I'd compute the gradient.
[SOUND] Yeah, and
then once I've got the gradient-
&gt;&gt; Stop, stop, stop.
This is deep learning.
&gt;&gt; What?
&gt;&gt; Not computer vision, deep learning.
&gt;&gt; No, no gradient?
&gt;&gt; No, focus.
Deep learning.
&gt;&gt; Got it.
Okay.
[SOUND] Then I think I'd
go fire up my simulator.
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
When you're done you're going to have an
awesome portfolio project to show off.
Actually that was kind of cool.
[SOUND]